Hey, what's up? Jeremiah Kowski here. I
want to show you one of the coolest AI
tools that's out there. All the
different AI tools that are out there
are improving all the time. They're
constantly getting better every month. I
mean, what I'm showing you now is going
to only get better in a month or two
from now. But there's a convergence, a
point, a moment in time where we're at
right now. It's December 5th, uh, 2025
where a lot of these tools have started
to mature at an incredible level. And so
I want to show you one of them, how we
used it to actually create an app that
we're about to launch here really soon
um, with a client business of mine and
how we did everything using uh, Gemini
Nano Banana Pro for graphics. Um, and
Lovable is the app that it is. Lovable
is this amazing
new
um, development app. Lovable.dev is what
the site is. And they have added in this
new version of it
called Lovable Cloud, which is really,
really cool. And so, Lovable Cloud, for
example,
includes
cloud access to AI tools and all of
that. And all you got to do is you
literally just chat with Lovable and
tell it what you wanted to create. This
is the one that we just created this
week right here. It's not launched yet,
but we created this. It's a it's a GPT
uh bot right here. It created the whole
landing page. It created all of the
membership functionality even with
member loginins. Members can log in,
they can access their memberships. You
know, if I just type in um you know, my
credentials right here, we can see,
okay, we can pay for it. We can access
it right here uh to ask questions. Um
it's an there's an admin panel where I
can take care of all this right here in
the back end.
uh dashboard where people can edit their
subscription. They can manage their
billing right here uh right in Stripe.
It has a full Stripe integration built
right in. And so this is incredible. We
did all of this just by prompting it. Um
and it it actually is the most perfect
uh usable outputs that we have seen of
any tools that we've been able to create
overall. So, that's what I want to show
you is I want to show you just kind of
how easy it is to to do this. What we're
going to do is we're going to actually
um let me see if I can log out of my
account here and I'm just going to show
you. Okay, so Lovable, when you land on
the site of Lovable, these are the two
tools that I would use. I would use
Lovable and then I would use
gemini.google.com, google.com which has
Nano Banana Pro right here under Gemini
Pro and I have a Nano Banana Pro Gemini
Pro account here right here um that I
can that I can use it gives me all of
these. Okay, so Nano Banana I can create
any kind of graphics or things that you
want and you can convert images into
graphics which is really incredible.
Create an image. I can do this, you
know. Um,
make me a header for a mental health app
that helps people
um who are dealing with mental health
issues using AI. You know, for instance,
now let's go into Lovable and let's
create a prototype of something like
this. And Lovable now, the new the new
version of Lovable, it goes beyond just
prototyping.
First off, you have all these templates
that you can use. It goes beyond just
prototyping to where you can actually
launch and create products inside of it
that make money. And so again, these are
these are templates that people have
created, tools that you could just clone
these projects as well um and use them
on your own if you want to, which is
really kind of incredible.
Okay, most popular. We have a
cryptocurrency. Let's see.
All this all this stuff is right here.
Build with Lovable. It's a co-founder on
your team. You can ship it inside of
Lovable. And now with Lovable Cloud, it
has uh full integrations with
um
just about everything that you can think
of for building this stuff out. Okay, so
let's log in. I'm going to log in here
to my account
and we're going to go build something.
And I'm going to just show you how easy
this is to do. Um, make me a mental
health app that uses uh AI
and offers a form of chat talk therapy.
It combines CBT and
uh internal family systems
into the
prompting. really focus on the system
prompt
and develop out the landing pages and
Stripe in integration
membership functionality.
Literally, I'm going to just prompt this
one single prompt right here. And with
Lovable Cloud, it's going to go ahead
and literally include all of this for
us. Now, with this, it's going to
essentially be able to create an app
that I could launch and charge money for
tomorrow if I wanted to. Um, so we're
going to add all these features. It's
going to do this. It's going to take a
little while to do this. I'm going to
pause the recording and then we're going
to come back once it's done kind of
processing all the different uh AI for
the version one right here.
And right now, it came up with a title,
MindBridge.
Let's go in. So, Nano Banana is doing
this right here. It's creating this
image. Um, we're we're going to call it
mindbridge.
Uh, make something that's a bit more
approachable and personal
and happy. Okay, that looks too too AI
focused. Let's make it look more
personal and approachable. You can use
Nano Banana Pro right here to make uh
graphics for you that you can use, which
is just incredible. Okay, so it's it's
going ahead. It's building all this out
right here. It's building out all the
all the code in the back end. What it's
actually doing is it's actually creating
all the files in the back end for this
um to have a site that you could review
and look at and be able to use. Okay.
And so again,
just watch as it starts to put this
together. We're going to come back. You
can see this. Here we go. MindBridge
connecting you to happiness and support.
This is great. Okay. All right.
All right. So, here's the landing page
that it's created right here. Look at
this. Mind bridge. This is a logo, how
it works, our approach, pricing,
um, start a conversation.
This is great. This is awesome.
We're adding all this. It's putting in a
database. It's adding in the AI tools,
the approaches. Here's the different
pricing on this.
This is awesome.
Now, here's the thing. I didn't
pre-record this. I haven't even tested
this out before. If this works and it
actually creates a full app for us that
we can use, my goodness, that's
incredible.
And right there, it's gone ahead and
created this app for us that we can use
this test right here. I literally was
able to go in, start free, and create
this talking chat app right here just
like this. It's incredible that you're
able to do this. It's incredible you're
able to put it together landing pages
and offers and things like that. The
possibilities are limitless for this for
you to get started and to use a tool
like this. And so again, I'd recommend
if you're a person who wants to build a
business, a software business, and use
tools like this, get lovable. Start
playing around with it. You can create
graphics with Nano Banana with Gemini.
It's a lot easier than it ever was to be
able to do stuff like this. And it's
totally worth it to take your time and
to learn these tools. They're a lot
easier than you think. They're totally
worth the time and energy that it takes
to test out, try them out, and see what
happens for you. Listen, if you're a
coach, if you're a mentor, you want to
get more clients online, you want to get
more people buying from you, my Wealthy
Coach Academy program walks you through
step by step exactly what to do to make
sure that you get more buyers in your
business, in your offers. I show you
exactly how to do it the right way. Make
sure that you jump in, check one of the
links in the bio below. We'll talk soon.
Have a good one everybody.